Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000; 27581
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1962-1963; cuid5772; 27707 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1964-1965; cuid5773; 27706 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1970-1979, 1982; cuid5774; 27705 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Grievances, 1958-1965; cuid5775; 27704 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963-1966; cuid5776; 27703 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Minutes, 1965; cuid5777; 27702 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1959-1965; cuid5778; 27701 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Local 1655 (Metropolitan Transit Authority, MTA, Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1955-1959; cuid5779; 27700 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1960; cuid5780; 27699 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1961-1963; cuid5781; 27698 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1964-1966, 1971-1976; cuid5782; 27697 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees), undated, 1979-1982; cuid5783; 27696 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Financial Reports, 1960-1963; cuid5784; 27695 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Grievances, 1960-1966; cuid5785; 27694 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966; cuid5786; 27693 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Minutes, 1957-1960; cuid5787; 27692 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Local 1655 (MTA Clerical-Administrative Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1965; cuid5788; 27691 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Local 1665 (Museum of the City of New York, MCNY), 1959-1965, 1982; cuid5789; 27690 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Local 1665 (MCNY): Grievances, 1962-1965; cuid5790; 27689 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Local 1665 (MCNY): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1960-1964; cuid5791; 27688 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Local 1665 (MCNY): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1959-1965; cuid5792; 27687 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations), 1959-1966, 1970; cuid5793; 27686 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations): Grievances, 1961-1967; cuid5794; 27685 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966; cuid5795; 27684 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Local 1674 (Supervisors of Parks Operations): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1960-1964; cuid5796; 27683 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts), 1962-1967, 1970-1975; cuid5797; 27682 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts): Grievances, 1963-1966; cuid5798; 27681 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963-1966; cuid5799; 27680 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Local 1757 (Assessors, Appraisers, and Mortgage Analysts): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1963-1965; cuid5800; 27679 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - Local 1759 (Consumer Affairs Inspectors), 1960-1967, 1971, 1975; cuid5801; 27678 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Local 1759 (Consumer Affairs Inspectors): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1963-1965; cuid5802; 27677 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Local 1759 (Consumer Affairs Inspectors): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1963-1964; cuid5803; 27676 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Local 1783 (Housing Authority Maintenance and Operations Employees), 1963; cuid5804; 27675 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1963-1964; cuid5805; 27674 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1965; cuid5806; 27673 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees), 1966-1967; cuid5807; 27672 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Grievances, 1964-1966; cuid5808; 27671 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Feb 1965-Sep 1965; cuid5809; 27670 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, Oct 1965-1966; cuid5810; 27669 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Minutes, 1963-1965, 1967; cuid5811; 27668 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Local 1784 (Department of Hospitals Professional and Clerical-Administrative Employees): Salary Appeal Briefs, 1963, 1966; cuid5812; 27667 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Local 1792 (Custodial Supervisors): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966; cuid5813; 27666 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Local 1795 (Maintenance Men), 1964-1965; cuid5814; 27665 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Local 1795 (Maintenance Men): Meeting Notices and Leaflets, 1964-1966; cuid5815; 27664 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Local 1795 (Maintenance Men): Stationary Firemen, 1970-1976, 1982; cuid5816; 27663 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Local 1797 (Custodial Supervisors), 1962-1966; cuid5817; 27662 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Local 1797 (Custodial Supervisors): Printed Material, 1971; cuid5818; 27661 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Local 1930 (New York Public Library Guild), 1967, 1970-1976, 1981; cuid5819; 27660 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Local 1930 (New York Public Library Guild): Newsletters, 1970-1976; 1981-1982; 1989; cuid5820; 27659 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Local 1931 (TBTA Maintenance Employees), 1972, 1982; cuid5821; 27658 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Local 2021 (Off-Track Betting Corporation, OTBC), 1970-1979; cuid5822; 27657 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Local 2021 (OTBC), 1980-1982, 1999; cuid5823; 27656 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Local 2021 (OTBC): Minutes, 1980-1981; cuid5824; 27655 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Local 2054 (College Assistants), 1970-1975, 1981-1982, 1997; cuid5825; 27654 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Local 2507 (Uniformed EMTs and Paramedics), 1975, 1981-1982; cuid5826; 27653 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Local 2627 (Electronic Data Processing Personnel), 1973-1976, 1981-1982, 1989; cuid5827; 27652 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Local 2906 (Marine Workers): Printed Material, 1976; cuid5828; 27651 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Locals: Lists, 1962, [1973?]; cuid5829; 27650 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Memoranda: General, 1972-1976; cuid5830; 27649 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Municipal Credit Union, 1976; cuid5831; 27648 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Municipal Employees Legal Services Plan (MELS), undated, 1975-1976, 1982; cuid5832; 27647 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Municipal Labor Committee, 1973-1975; cuid5833; 27646 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - National Black Nurses Association, 1997; cuid5834; 27645 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - New Jersey Department of Labor and Industry Report: Upgrading Community Service Aides in a Public Housing Agency I, 1969; cuid5835; 27644 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - New Jersey Department of Labor and Industry Report: Upgrading Community Service Aides in a Public Housing Agency II, 1969; cuid5836; 27643 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - New York City Board of Education, 1961-1966; cuid5837; 27642 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - New York City Board of Education: Meeting Calendars, 1963-1965; cuid5838; 27641 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - New York City Board of Education: Press Releases, 1961-1962; cuid5839; 27640 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - New York City Board of Education: Salary Schedules, 1961-1963; cuid5840; 27639 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - New York City Board of Education: Summary of Citywide Reading Test Results, 1968-1969; cuid5841; 27638 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - New York City Budget, 1978; cuid5842; 27637 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - New York City Budget, 1984; cuid5843; 27636 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - New York City Budget, 1985; cuid5844; 27635 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - New York City Budget, 1986; cuid5845; 27634 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - New York City Equal Employment Opportunity Policy, 1996; cuid5846; 27633 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation (NYC HHC): Board Briefing Book, 1996; cuid5847; 27632 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - NYC HHC: Special Board Meeting, 1996; cuid5848; 27631 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - New York State Budget: DC 37 Response, 1996; cuid5849; 27630 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - New York Workers' Rights Board, 1998; cuid5850; 27629 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Parks Policy Committee, 1965-1966; cuid5851; 27628 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - PEOPLE Committee, 1982, 1986; cuid5852; 27627 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Political Action, 1970; cuid5853; 27626 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Political Action, 1971-1973; cuid5854; 27625 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Political Action, 1974-1976; cuid5855; 27624 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Political Action, 1981; cuid5856; 27623 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Political Action, 1981-1982, 1989; cuid5857; 27622 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Political Action: City Council Campaign (Mary Pinkett), 1985; cuid5858; 27621 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Political Action: City Council Committee on Civil Service and Labor, 1978-1987; cuid5859; 27620 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Political Action: City Council Committee on Health, 1983; cuid5860; 27619 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Political Action: City Council Committee on Health, 1986; cuid5861; 27618 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Political Action: Congressional Campaign (Terry Benbow), 1984; cuid5862; 27617 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Political Action: Elections I, 1982; cuid5863; 27616 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Political Action: Elections II, 1982; cuid5864; 27615 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Political Action: Elections, 1983; cuid5865; 27614 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Political Action: Elections I, 1984-1985; cuid5866; 27613 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Political Action: Elections II, 1984-1985; cuid5867; 27612 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Political Action: Elections III, 1984-1985; cuid5868; 27611 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Political Action: Elections IV, 1984-1985, 1992; cuid5869; 27610 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Political Action: Elections (Oversize), 1982; cuid5870; 27609 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Political Action: Opposition to MVO Contract with Vera Institute of Justice, 1989-1990; cuid5871; 27608 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Walter Mondale), 1983-1984; cuid5872; 27607 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Political Action: Screening Committee, 1980; cuid5873; 27606 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Political Action: Screening Committee, 1986; cuid5874; 27605 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Professional Division: Leaflets, 1970-1971; cuid5875; 27604 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Professional Services: Reports, undated; cuid5876; 27603 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Quality of Work Life Program, 1993-1995; cuid5877; 27602 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Retirees and Cultural Affairs Department, 1971-1976, 1985-1986; cuid5878; 27601 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Safety and Health Unit, 1982; cuid5879; 27600 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - School Crossing Guards Organizing Campaign, 1974-1975, 1978-1980; cuid5880; 27599 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Shop Stewards Manual, 1964; cuid5881; 27598 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Summer Hours Dispute, 1966; cuid5882; 27597 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Test Manual, undated; cuid5883; 27596 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Test Preparation Course: Supervising Clerk-Stenographer, 1971; cuid5884; 27595 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Test Preparation Manual: Supervising Clerk (Income Maintenance), ca.1962; cuid5885; 27594 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Publicity, 1961-1962; cuid5886; 27593 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Strike Clippings, 1967-1968; cuid5887; 27592 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Vietnam War, 1970; cuid5888; 27591 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Women's Committee, 1982-1984, 1990; cuid5889; 27590 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Oversize Materials., 27588
    - NOTE: This box holds oversize materials; individual folders are listed where they would normally appear in the finding-aid., undated; cuid5890; 27589 (Box 60)
- Series VI: Restricted Materials, 1967-1997; 27582
  Conditions Governing Access
  Materials in this series are closed for privacy reasons and will be opened 50 years after their date of creation.
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries) (Restricted), 1967; cuid5891; 27587 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - CETA Questionnaire (Restricted), 1979; cuid5892; 27586 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Local 420 Members' Petition (Restricted), 1979; cuid5893; 27585 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association v. Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Lukas et al. v. Ascher et al.) (Restricted), 1996; cuid5894; 27584 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153 (Restricted), 1997; cuid5895; 27583 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Series VII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Reels, 1977-1990; 310561
  - Subseries VII:A: "It's Your City, It's Our Job" Radio Show Audio Reels, 1986-1990., 310572
    - Bridges, May 29, [?]; cuid5896; 310585 (Box 62, Reel 1)
    - Local 299, Undated; cuid5897; 310586 (Box 62, Reel 2)
    - Local 299 Recreation, Jun 25, [?]; cuid5898; 310587 (Box 62, Reel 3)
    - [Music and Songs] (Master Copy), Undated; cuid5899; 310588 (Box 62, Reel 4)
    - [Unidentified], Nov 15, [?]; cuid5900; 310589 (Box 62, Reel 5)
    - [Unidentified], Nov 22, [?]; cuid5901; 310590 (Box 62, Reel 6)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Parts I and II, Dec 18, 1986; cuid5902; 310591 (Box 62, Reel 7)
    - Women at Work, Mar 5, 1987; cuid5903; 310592 (Box 62, Reel 8)
    - New York City Botanical Gardeners, Mar 26, 1987; cuid5904; 310593 (Box 62, Reel 9)
    - March on Washington, Apr 9, 1987; cuid5905; 310594 (Box 62, Reel 10)
    - Recreation Program, May 7, 1987; cuid5906; 310595 (Box 62, Reel 11)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Labor History, May 21, 1987; cuid5907; 310596 (Box 63, Reel 12)
    - Safety and Health, Jun 4, 1987; cuid5908; 310597 (Box 63, Reel 13)
    - Summer Recreation, Jun 25, 1987; cuid5909; 310598 (Box 63, Reel 14)
    - Work With the Homeless, Jul 23, 1987; cuid5910; 310599 (Box 63, Reel 15)
    - Emergency Medical Services, Oct 21, 1987; cuid5911; 310600 (Box 63, Reel 16)
    - Puerto Rican Heritage Week, Nov 8, 1987; cuid5912; 310601 (Box 63, Reel 17)
    - Whistleblowers, Nov 22, 1987; cuid5913; 310602 (Box 63, Reel 18)
    - 911 Technicians, Jan 3, 1988; cuid5914; 310603 (Box 63, Reel 19)
    - New York Public Health System, Jan 19, 1988; cuid5915; 310604 (Box 63, Reel 20)
    - Black History Month, Feb 3, 1988; cuid5916; 310605 (Box 63, Reel 21)
    - Black History Month (Working Dub), Feb 24, 1988; cuid5917; 310606 (Box 63, Reel 22)
    - Black History Month (Master Copy), Feb 24, 1988; cuid5918; 310607 (Box 63, Reel 23)
    - Museums, May 1, 1988; cuid5919; 310608 (Box 64, Reel 24)
    - Tax Assessors, May 15, 1988; cuid5920; 310609 (Box 64, Reel 25)
    - Museums, Jun 12, 1988; cuid5921; 310610 (Box 64, Reel 26)
    - Public Libraries, Jun 26, 1988; cuid5922; 310611 (Box 64, Reel 27)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 1 and 2, Jul 10, 1988; cuid5923; 310612 (Box 64, Reel 28, Box WAG ACCESS 1)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 3 and 4, Jul 24, 1988 [?]; cuid5924; 310613 (Box 64, Reel 29, Box WAG ACCESS 1)
      Scope and Content Note
      For small portion of recording, second audio content at different speed heard under the main content which resulted in a brief decrease in sound quality.
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 5 and 6, Jul 17, 1988 [?]; cuid5925; 310616 (Box 64, Reel 30, Box WAG ACCESS 1)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 7 and 8, 1988; cuid5926; 310617 (Box 64, Reel 31, Box WAG ACCESS 1)
    - Come to the Cabaret (Dec 23); Hurricane Relief Committees (Jan 6), 1988-1989; cuid5927; 310618 (Box 64, Reel 32)
    - [Intro and Closing], Apr 9, 1990; cuid5928; 310619 (Box 64, Reel 33)
    - [Intro, Closing, and Promos], Apr 9, 1990; cuid5929; 310620 (Box 64, Reel 34)
  - Subseries VII:B: Other DC 37 Audio Reels, 1985-1990., 310623
    - "Negotiation" (Radio Spots featuring Baylin, Riccio, and Mariano), Jan 9, 1985; cuid5930; 310627 (Box 65, Reel 35)
    - "Coalition" (Radio Spots featuring Wondolowski, Johnson, Arlene Baylor, and Marco Castro), Jan 15, 1985; cuid5931; 310628 (Box 65, Reel 36)
    - "Haven't We Learned Anything from the 70s?" (Speech by Stanley Hill), Oct 1, 1990; cuid5932; 310629 (Box 65, Reel 37)
    - "Contract Rally" (Radio Spot by Stanley Hill), Nov 2, 1990; cuid5933; 310630 (Box 65, Reel 38)
    - "Just Like You" (Speech by Stanley Hill), Dec 23, 1990; cuid5934; 310631 (Box 65, Reel 39)
  - Subseries VII:C: Non-DC 37 Audio Reels, 1977-1980., 310634
    - Crossroads: "Women in China" (NPR Program), Aug 11, 1977; cuid5935; 310637 (Box 65, Reel 40)
    - The Mind's Eye: "Cowboy" (NPR Program by Josh Darsa), Oct 4, 1980; cuid5936; 310638 (Box 65, Reel 41)
- Series VIII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Cassettes, 1986-1999; 310566
  - Subseries VIII:A: "It's Your City, It's Our Job" Audio Cassettes, 1986-1998., 310639
    - DC37 Theme Song, Undated; cuid5937; 310640 (Box 66, Cassette 42)
    - EMS Employees, Undated; cuid5938; 310641 (Box 66, Cassette 43)
    - Holiday/Christmas Show, Undated; cuid5939; 310642 (Box 66, Cassette 44)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated; cuid5940; 310643 (Box 66, Cassette 45)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated; cuid5941; 310644 (Box 66, Cassette 46)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated; cuid5942; 310645 (Box 66, Cassette 47)
    - Shop Stewards, undated; cuid5943; 593088 (Box 67, Cassette 148)
    - Budget Smarts, undated; cuid5944; 593089 (Box 67, Cassette 149)
    - Wurf, Mildred and Elma Osborne, May 26, [?]; cuid5945; 310646 (Box 66, Cassette 48)
    - Kids, School, and Drugs, Oct 2, 1986; cuid5946; 310647 (Box 66, Cassette 49)
    - Drugs in Schools (part 1), Oct 9, 1986; cuid5947; 310648 (Box 66, Cassette 50-53)
    - Drugs in Schools (part 2), Oct 9, 1986; cuid5948; 310649 (Box 66, Cassette 54-55)
    - Able But Disabled, Oct 16, 1986; cuid5949; 310650 (Box 66, Cassette 56-57)
    - Able But Disabled (part 1), Oct 16, 1986; cuid5950; 310651 (Box 66, Cassette 58-62)
    - Able But Disabled (part 2), Oct 16, 1986; cuid5951; 310652 (Box 66, Cassette 63-66)
    - Politics and Poker, Oct 30, 1986; cuid5952; 310653 (Box 66, Cassette 67)
    - Union Memories, Dec 4, 1986; cuid5953; 310661 (Box 66, Cassette 68)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 11, 1986; cuid5954; 310662 (Box 66, Cassette 69)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 18, 1986; cuid5955; 310663 (Box 66, Cassette 70)
    - Work With the Homeless, Jan 8, 1987; cuid5956; 310664 (Box 66, Cassette 71)
    - The Homeless, Jan 15, 1987; cuid5957; 310665 (Box 66, Cassette 72)
    - Talking Union (with Frank Morelli and Stanley Hill), Jan 28, 1987; cuid5958; 310666 (Box 66, Cassette 73)
    - Talking Union (with Frank Morelli and Stanley Hill), Jan 29, 1987; cuid5959; 310667 (Box 66, Cassette 74)
    - Black History Program, Feb 12, 1987; cuid5960; 310668 (Box 66, Cassette 75)
    - Black History Month, Feb 26, 1987; cuid5961; 310669 (Box 66, Cassette 76)
    - Women at Work, Mar 5, 1987; cuid5962; 310670 (Box 66, Cassette 77-78)
    - Gardening, Apr 2, 1987; cuid5963; 310671 (Box 66, Cassette 79)
    - March on Washington, Apr 9, 1987; cuid5964; 310672 (Box 66, Cassette 80)
    - The Bronx Zoo, Apr 23, 1987; cuid5965; 310673 (Box 66, Cassette 81)
    - New York City Recreation, May 7, 1987; cuid5966; 310674 (Box 66, Cassette 82)
    - Labor History, May 21, 1987; cuid5967; 310675 (Box 66, Cassette 83)
    - Occupational Health and Safety Administration (OSHA), Jun 4, 1987; cuid5968; 310676 (Box 66, Cassette 84-85)
    - Summer in the City, Jun 25, 1987; cuid5969; 310677 (Box 66, Cassette 86-87)
    - New Announcer Introduction, Promo, and Closing, Oct 5, 1987; cuid5970; 310678 (Box 66, Cassette 88)
    - 911 Technicians, Oct 11, 1987; cuid5971; 310679 (Box 66, Cassette 89)
    - Emergency Medical Services, Oct 25, 1987; cuid5972; 310680 (Box 66, Cassette 90-91)
    - Music (You Can Be Happy, Celestial Choir), Oct 25, 1987; cuid5973; 310681 (Box 66, Cassette 92)
    - Puerto Rican Heritage, Nov 11, 1987; cuid5974; 310682 (Box 66, Cassette 93)
    - Whistleblowers, Nov 22, 1987; cuid5975; 310683 (Box 66, Cassette 94)
    - Domestic Violence, Dec 6 ,1987; cuid5976; 310684 (Box 66, Cassette 95)
    - Domestic Violence, Jan 17, 1988; cuid5977; 310685 (Box 66, Cassette 96)
    - Public Health System Nurses, Jan 31, 1988; cuid5978; 310686 (Box 66, Cassette 97)
    - Black History Month, Feb 3, 1988; cuid5979; 310687 (Box 66, Cassette 98)
    - Hughes, Charles and Stanley Hill, Feb 18, 1988; cuid5980; 310688 (Box 66, Cassette 99)
    - Eldridge, Ron and Cream Tea, Feb 19, 1988; cuid5981; 310689 (Box 66, Cassette 100)
    - Ibrahim, Abdullah (Local 371), Feb 19, 1988; cuid5982; 310690 (Box 66, Cassette 101)
    - Black History, Feb 28, 1988; cuid5983; 310691 (Box 66, Cassette 102)
    - Women's History, Mar 30, 1988; cuid5984; 310692 (Box 66, Cassette 103)
    - Public Libraries, Apr 10, 1988; cuid5985; 310693 (Box 66, Cassette 104)
    - New York Museums, May 8, 1988; cuid5986; 310694 (Box 66, Cassette 105)
    - Tax Assessors, May 15, 1988; cuid5987; 310695 (Box 66, Cassette 106)
    - New York Bridges, May 29, 1988; cuid5988; 310696 (Box 66, Cassette 107)
    - The Other Island, Jun 12, 1988; cuid5989; 310697 (Box 66, Cassette 108)
    - Presidential Election (Oct 18, 1988)/Sewage Treatment Workers (Nov 1, 1988), cuid5990; 310698 (Box 66, Cassette 109)
    - People's Court (Nov 29, 1988)/Holiday Headaches (1988), cuid5991; 310699 (Box 66, Cassette 110)
    - Holiday Show, Dec 7, 1988; cuid5992; 310700 (Box 66, Cassette 111)
    - Come to the Cabaret (Dec 13, 1988)/People Helping People (Jan 10, 1989), 1988-1989; cuid5993; 310701 (Box 66, Cassette 112)
    - Hospitals in Crisis, Jan 31, 1989; cuid5994; 310702 (Box 66, Cassette 113)
    - Hospitals in Crisis (Jan 31, 1989)/Black History (Feb 14, 1989), Jan-Feb, 1989; cuid5995; 310703 (Box 66, Cassette 114)
    - Shop Stewards (Mar 7, 1989)/Women's Work (Mar 21, 1989), Mar 1989; cuid5996; 310704 (Box 66, Cassette 115)
    - City Infrastructure (Apr 4, 1989)/PSU Outreach Program (Apr 18, 1989), Apr 1989; cuid5997; 310705 (Box 66, Cassette 116)
    - Today's Technology, Tomorrow's Health (May 2, 1989)/CUNY Crisis (May 16, 1989), May 1989; cuid5998; 310706 (Box 66, Cassette 117)
    - Active Retirees (May 30, 1989)/Off-Track Betting (OTB) Employees (Jun 13, 1989), May-Jun 1989; cuid5999; 310707 (Box 66, Cassette 118)
    - Central Park Zoo (Jun 27, 1989)/Kids, Crime, Counselors (Jul 11, 1989), Jun-Jul 1989; cuid6000; 310708 (Box 66, Cassette 119)
    - Health Care Funding, Oct 17, 1989; cuid6001; 310709 (Box 66, Cassette 120-121)
    - Public Services International (PSI) Report, Dec 5, 1989; cuid6002; 310710 (Box 66, Cassette 122)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 13, 1989; cuid6003; 310711 (Box 66, Cassette 123)
    - Reading Comprehension (Jan 30, 1991)/Educational Fund (N.D.), cuid6004; 310712 (Box 66, Cassette 124)
    - Educational Fund-Supervisory Skills for APP Test Preparation Series, Feb 27, 1991; cuid6005; 310713 (Box 66, Cassette 125)
    - Rally Special, Sep 3, 1991; cuid6006; 310714 (Box 66, Cassette 126)
    - Black History Month, Feb 10, 1992; cuid6007; 310715 (Box 66, Cassette 127)
    - Hispanic Heritage--Jose Labor, 1994 August 30; cuid6008; 593090 (Box 67, Cassette 150)
    - Harlem-New City, Oct 17, 1994; cuid6009; 310716 (Box 66, Cassette 128)
    - Contract on America, Jan 1995; cuid6010; 310717 (Box 66, Cassette 129-130)
    - Post-Holiday Bills Blues, Jan 20, 1995; cuid6011; 310718 (Box 67, Cassette 131)